Vinayak Ghadigaokar

IT Operations and Support

Laxmi Nagar, Ghatkopar (E), Mumbai - 400 075 •

(+91) 8104709152 •

- vghadigaokar2408@gmail.com •
- www.linkedin.com/in/vinayakghadigaokar •

OBJECTIVE

6+ Years Experienced professional looking for a challenging role in a fintech organisation to utilize my skills towards the growth of organisation as well to enhance my knowledge about new and emerging trends in Banking, Digital Payments and IT sector.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Kiya.ai (Infrasoft Technologies Pvt Ltd)

Senior Associate Consultant,

(June 2022 - Present)

- Project Implementation, Maintaining client's Issue Register and provide resolution.
- Release Testing and deployment of Web Application
- Deploying Reports on Visual Studio, Joining tables to validate correctness of data

NKGSB BANK

Clerk, (June 2018 – June 2022)

- NFS , Rupay , IMPS, UPI Reconciliation
- Automation of various charges in Finacle
- Dealing with ATM switch vendor Euronet for ATM other transactional log related issues
- Generation of E- Channels MIS Reports for Management and Accounts
- Tickets Resolution on RedMine (Finacle Support to the Branches related to user access/ATM transactions / process or flow of particular module)
- UAT for Internet Banking and Mobile Banking Application
- Contribution to project implementation green pin UAT
- Assistance in management's strategic decisions in meetings
- Sound knowledge of Branch Banking operations (CASA Term deposits/ Loan/NEFT/RTGS/Locker/Teller)

Genius Consultants

Associate

(October 2016 - May 2018)

- Worked on TCS TAG project and Merck Life Science Pvt Ltd Customer Support Team.
- At Merck worked on Providing solutions to retailer's problems (about order status, Availability of different chemicals)
- Generating road permits for harmful chemicals post GST implementation
- Processing credit notes to retailers
- Specifically appreciated by CEO Mr. Kevin Gorman for exemplary performance
- At TCS worked under TAG Support to career portal users via e mail and chat, Sending Mass Mailers
- ❖ Awarded STAR Performer for responding to 200 queries within a day

Education Certifications

- ❖ MBA IT and Systems NMIMS(Dec 2022)
- Bcom attended GNIIT software engineering course (May 2016)
- ♦ HSC (May 2013)
- ❖ SSC

Microsoft SQL Training Intellipaat (Oct 2022)